Grant Kee

Life-long learner with a passion for coding. Diligent and detail-oriented, professional and positive. Experience with web development, creative problem solving, and learning new skills; strong and effective communicator. I bring a lot of energy and focus on securing success for the entire team.

EXPERIENCE

Travis Medical Sales Corporation, Austin — Funding Coordinator

June 2018 - Present

Currently creating a search application for assigning HCPCS Procedure Codes to complex rehabilitation equipment, primarily custom manual and power wheelchairs. Process health records for new clients in need of durable medical equipment. Coordinate with medical professionals and insurance representatives. Provide excellent customer service. Train new employees. Focus on sales goals while maintaining low cost of goods.

The Pen is Mightier Content Creators, Austin — *Tech. Writer*

September 2017 - June 2018

Understand and develop business strategies for companies to attract new clients. Content creation for websites; creatively convince viewers to purchase services. Swiftly adapt to new search engine optimization techniques to increase visibility and web presence for clients.

Cicis Pizza, Woodbridge, VA — Assistant General Manager

January 2016 - December 2016 (went back to complete my degree)

Over \$1.3 million in annual sales; consistently top 5 in sales on East Coast; managing employees, hiring, and training employees; experience handling money, ordering produce, certified by corporate to manage Cicis locations nationwide; sales increased by 12% under my leadership.

EDUCATION

Austin Coding Academy, Austin — JavaScript Full Stack Developer Program

April 2019 - Present

Teaching Assistant for Web 101 Course; dedicated tutor; I've learned how to create servers, manipulate the DOM, automate testing, read documentation, research solutions to find the best practice, review code for efficiency to enhance performance; master the material by helping others. Currently mastering React and Redux. Graduate February 1, 2020.

The University of Texas, Austin — Biology BSA with Business Foundations Certificate

Graduated in August 2017

Emerging Scholars Program; Freshman Research Initiative; Research apprenticeship - Synthesis and Biological Recognition Stream; UTeach Internship - Outreach Section Leader; Phi Mu Alpha - Music Fraternity

15017 Harkness Pass Austin, TX 78725 (817) 614 5289 grant.d.kee@gmail.com github.com/grantkee

SKILLS

Self-driven
Teamwork
Critical Thinking
Communication
Fast Learner
Technical Writing

CODING EXPERIENCE

JavaScript: Vanilla, Node.js, React, Redux, Express, JQuery, TypeScript MySQL, HTML, CSS

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Employee of the Month Oct 2019

Freshman Research Initiative

Emerging Scholars Program

UTeach Internship

Research Apprenticeship -Synthesis and Biological Recognition Stream

Eagle Scout - Troop 68 Senior Patrol Leader; backpacking mentor; nature enthusiast

Interests

No Agenda Podcast -Music Producer

Copastatic - musician; vocals, bass, keyboard, guitar, sound production

Ulster Project - dedicated to reducing sectarian violence in Northern Ireland through community service